Oh, what is that? A latex jumpsuit? Isn't that like what all the celebrities are wearing at the moment?
It looks so good. I want to look like Kim Kardashian too. I'm ordering it.
Oh, who can it be? Maybe the mailman?
Hello, I'm your postman. I have something for you.
Oh it's my super awesome celebrity latex outfit!
Oh what is that? It's not shiny at all!
And it smells like tires!
Oh it's so sticky!
Oh I'm super disappointed!
If you want to know the story about this unusual intro and why I bought this latex catsuit for only 18€, you should watch this video.
By the way, this is going to be a really long video, so if you want to find certain topics
or outfits, just use the chapters.
Hi everyone and welcome to this new video.
It's a really special one because I'm having a look at latex clothing sold by fast fashion
stores.
I'm going to show you three pieces today, a bodysuit and a dress by House of McQuee
and a latex catsuit from Fashion Nova.
I found all of them online at the home page of these fast fashion stores.
And before I'm telling you more, I'm going to switch into the first dress.
This dress is called Santa Electric Rose, the V Butterfly Sleeves Latex Dress by House
of McQueer.
It's originally £149 and I bought it on sale for £49 only.
size extra small and I have a few issues with it to be honest with everything I
saw so far but let's start the fit is not really great I don't love it it's
somehow too wide here a bit and it feels like it's just cut off somewhere without
without thinking where and it's also a bit too wide although it's size extra small.
The zipper looks really bulky and too long so there are a lot of ruffles here and it
does not lay very smooth on my body which is like the thing of latex to stick to the
latex to stick to the body really close but it doesn't really do that when I'm moving around.
Where the zipper ends it's not even but it's like a step between the two sides so not
not how it's supposed to look. At one place at the zipper there's also a lump of something. I don't
know it's really I don't know what they did there but it's not a really good workmanship. Another
real issue is that I don't seem to get it like really shiny because I shined it
I washed it twice and shined it and shined it now again and it's not not
really shiny it's dull somehow I don't know why maybe it's the quality of the
latex I know that for people who are not that into latex or not as experienced it
may seem like it's really shiny but I do own a lot of latex pieces I have some
experience and I can definitely say it's not really shiny and it's supposed to
shine more or be shinier or whatever and I don't know why I'm not and I'm not
able to shine it up properly I don't know and also now the real deep dive
here I do know how to do latex garments and I can tell you that the panels are
glued from outside to inside like the outside overlapping the inside panel and
normally you do it the other way around like the inside panel should overlap the
outside panel so that you have a smooth look and not have these edges here in
front of the dress but looking like at the back so something you don't do and
another real bad thing and if you would wear this multiple times it's supposed
to happen that here in front is going to rip because you have a lot of tension
here at this deep V point in the middle here and it's pulling the sides to each
side so a lot of tension and no reinforcement here so probably it'll rip
sometime right here in the middle downwards especially if you're not used
to getting into latex and you like pull and I don't know pull too much or
whatever it's going to rip here I can tell so there's a reinforcement missing
let's basically it on a positive note it came in a bag and inside this bag there was a whole page of
instructions on how to clean it and how to wear it also concerning latex allergy because some people
are illogical to just latex and yeah cleaning a lot of warnings how to wear it and so this is
is a real plus point that they're telling to people what to do with it
thumbs up for that for the rest of the dress I'm not really convinced and to
summarize all that I read that it's manufactured in People's Republic of
China so if I compare that price to the quality and to the established Western
latex designers it's not a good deal not at all it's the manufacturing is like
really cheap and clearly they misregarded some of the basic rules here like reinforcing and
gluing the sheets on top of each other also the seams are really thick which is okay um some
people like the look of them i prefer them a bit thinner and yeah as i said not really satisfied
here. Also when I look at the bodysuit which I'm going to wear next, there's a label inside
and you can't really read the label. Why even do a label then? But I think I'm going to
change into the bodysuit now because I've seen enough of the dress. The second piece
is the bodysuit and I can tell that I'm going to have the same issues again with the reinforcement
here and the cut whatsoever. Also I found a big patch of glue at the shoulder
which wasn't removed and doesn't leave a good impression either. And I have to say
that this one is size small and it somehow fits better than the size extra
small from the dress before yeah another Mysterium with the sizes in one company
they differ so much this one was originally 80 pounds and I bought it for
29 pounds so everything on sale and let's take a moment and think why is
is that? Probably because no one bought these things. As I said before I found
the items at fast fashion stores so their customers are normally not used to
latex. They probably didn't even know that it was latex maybe? I don't know I'll
get into that a little later. And they were on sale over half a year so you still get
them on sale like no one buys them. Oh I can turn around if you want to. Like I
said it kind of fits better than a dress although it's a size bigger okay let's
do this one and I didn't try it on so far I don't know what will happen okay
let's talk about this intro of the video in which you saw my distant cousin
Chantal or someone else? I don't know. Anyway, I made this intro because I found this catsuit on the Fashion Nova page
amongst a lot of PVC clothing and other latex clothes and the first weird thing
was that Fashion Nova calls this latex which is true but also calls PVC in a
lot of cases latex which is not true because it's PVC so they confused the
customers by calling stuff latex that isn't and adding real latex into their
product range and then I had a look at the reviews under these real latex
pieces and had a good laugh about them and I can read some of them to you
because it's so funny ripped like a pop balloon this item is not clothing it's a latex balloon
i tried to put it on the first time and it stuck to my body and wouldn't go up i was in a hurry
and left it alone hoping to try on with type powder or something as i read they could help
avoiding sticking to the body good on you should have returned it right away with text and all
fast forward to a couple months later when i had a real event that i needed to wear the outfit too
if you can call it that. It's a bit too late to wear it just right before the event.
Okay. I was extra careful not to let it stick to my body and halfway up my body
the top part of the suit just popped like a balloon and continued all the way
up. I never seen anything like it. I just want my money back Fashion Nova. It is
also not shiny as pictured. More of a matte look. Sorry, but this is just hilarious. Selling
latex to people who don't know anything about latex makes this happen. This really bad one
star review because clearly she has not any idea about what she's doing or that it's of
course not shiny because she has to shine it and all the stuff doesn't look
at all like picture proper ripped off wish I could return it but it's too
dearly to send back to fashion it's going in the bin well sorry but if you
do only think it's a ripoff because it's not shine when it arrives then yeah just
to stupid you will it takes a year from another dress poor quality this dress
smelled and looked like a big red balloon for what it cost this dress is not worth it
yeah well latex and balloons which are made of basically latex yeah but still two different
things okay next one a hot mess beware this dress is latex just like rubber gloves i didn't notice
you have to literally do so much to just put it on after even you have to let and even after you
have to add latex shine who has that time i can't even return it don't be fooled this dress isn't
at all isn't it or what sorry and yeah you have to shine it and yeah it is really latex although
i have to put this on fashion over to call just everything latex that isn't latex and latex that
is latex anyway people who people who buy latex should be aware of the fact
that you need time to put it on latex needs special care so fashion over
should either highlight that in the article or just make an extra category
on the side like real latex products but this is just confusing the customers who
of course are not going to buy it then and they will not make any money out of
of it of course because no one buys it.
Huge disappointment.
Nothing like the picture.
Came covered in powder that you find on gloves and is pale matte dark blue.
Not shiny.
It's hard to fit.
Sticks to your skin and even harder to get off.
For such cheap material it's not worth the price.
I got 5XL too snug.
Ah I was really cheering for this top.
Please revamp this idea.
Oh my god.
For such cheap material it's not worth the price.
Girl, this material is way more expensive than your normal cotton fabric.
Fast fashion stores as Fashion Nova or House of Megui, they degrade latex somehow, or not
somehow, they really degrade latex because they sell it to people who have no idea about
the material and to really dislike the material then because they have no clue about it.
And so, latex has even worse reputation.
And this is a story about the intro because I read all the comments and reviews and I
was like, girl, no, you're not getting this right.
Okay, back to the actual catsuit here.
Maybe you noticed I got two of them.
One in size small and one in size extra small because I bought one for 19 Euro.
So I thought I'm going to buy two because it's only 19 euros so I can choose which one
fits better because it's just 19 euros.
But I decided on the extra small and it's not horrible.
It fits.
It's a bit too short maybe but it has a better fit than the two items of House of Megui and
And I'm absolutely positively surprised about the trims in the neck and also the legs.
They reinforced the hemlines with another strip of latex.
So thumbs up for that.
Other than that, I'm not really sure about this bust seam here because that's not how
you do it with latex.
You can't really just take a cut from a normal fabric piece and use it one to one on latex.
not how it works and the latex sheet material makes a better impression than
the pink and the light pink one so to say so yeah even though fashion nova is
the cheaper fast fashion store their latex leaves a better impression here in
this video okay well that was my two cents about fast fashion selling latex
pieces as I said have a look at fashion nova or house of Megui they still have
latex items on sale if you buy something there leave me a comment or write me a
message tell me about it or do you already own something like that what do
you think of the intro because it was something different I can say also from
filming it it was really funny and yeah I hope you had fun with this video and
you enjoyed this topic and could learn something or yeah know something more
now than before anyway I hope you have a pleasant day see you in the next video
Bye!